Eduardo Elías Chacón

- Portfolio
- Buenos Aires, Argentina.
- Linkedin
- eduardo.elias.1192@gmail.com
- GitHub

Professional Profile

Professional with experience in web development and customer service. Standing out for advanced technical programming skills and a focused approach to customer satisfaction. Able to combine software development knowledge with strong sales and technical support experience to provide comprehensive and effective solutions.

Work Experience

Web Developer Front-End - Igrowker

June 2023 - Present

 Development of a mobile-first web app aimed at efficiently managing events. This project is designed to generate positive impact and growth in developers' skills and competencies, ensuring technical and commercial viability.

Web Developer Front-End - Makisan Tech

June 2023 - December 2023

 Development and maintenance of applications and web pages, to improve the user experience and optimize project performance.

Customer Service - Manpower Inc

March 2017 - February 2019

 Resolution of technical problems, sales and promotions, technical support, account management, complaint handling, case tracking, achievement of objectives.

Customer Service - Movilnet

September 2013 - November 2016

• Resolution of customer queries and complaints, technical support in telecommunications services, customer satisfaction guarantee.

Academic Training

Full Stack Developer Core - Digital Nao x Tecmilenio

October 2023 - May 2024

Interdisciplinary web development:

- Front End (user-facing interfaces and systems)
- Back End (logic, servers, and databases)

Developer Full-Stack - Egg Cooperation

December 2022 - September 2023

• Introduction to programming, Java, MySQL databases and React, is. It also included aspects such as object-oriented programming, exception handling and database connections.

Web Developer Front-End - Eidos Global-Accenture

March 2023 - June 2023

 Program designed to strengthen skills in Front End technologies, such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and GitHub, with the aim of enhancing web development and collaboration on projects.



Technical Skills

- Java
- JavaScript
- React JS
- Astro
- Node JS
- HTML & CSS
- Spring MVCTailwind-CSS
- Bootstrap
- Github
- MySQL Postman
- 0.....
- Jira
- WordpressTrello
- Notion
- Miro
- Figma
- 141110
- Vercel

Technical Skills

- Optimal Systems Management
- Optimization of Processes
- Computer Consulting
- Computer Assistance
- Customer Service
- Quality Control
- Technical Support

Soft Skills

- Logical and Analytical Thinking
- Effective Communication
- Attention to Details
- Time management
- Teamwork
- Adaptability
- Creativity

Languages

- Spanish Native
- English A2